[
{"question":"sav",
    "options":{"a":"sa","b":"da","c":"sa","d":"ra"},
    "answers":"b"
},

{
    "question":"ba vb",
    "options":{"a":"sb","b":"db","c":"sb","d":"rb"},
    "answers":"c"
},
{
    "question":"as opdf",
    "options":{"a":"sn","b":"dq","c":"su","d":"rp"},
    "answers":"a"
},
{
    "question":"asnmdf jak",
    "options":{"a":"sh","b":"du","c":"sp","d":"ri"},
    "answers":"d"
},
{
    "question":"asoapdf iaoa",
    "options":{"a":"sio","b":"dpo","c":"slp","d":"roi"},
    "answers":"a"
},
{
    "question":"as dfanm kakj",
    "options":{"a":"sml","b":"dop","c":"spo","d":"rio"},
    "answers":"c"
},
{
    "question":"asopd fdw",
    "options":{"a":"sn","b":"di","c":"sp","d":"rm"},
    "answers":"b"
},
{
    "question":"asks dftwy",
    "options":{"a":"sio","b":"dsks","c":"sui","d":"rbns"},
    "answers":"b"
},
{
    "question":"abss dfuis",
    "options":{"a":"sio","b":"dm","c":"sr","d":"rpps"},
    "answers":"d"
},
{
    "question":"asbns dfjsks",
    "options":{"a":"sw","b":"dpo","c":"snp","d":"rioe"},
    "answers":"a"
}

]